very playful,
now i'm going to replace the truffles here or here.
I'm thinking of investing only in truffles in real life,
because it sells too fast.
it's on,
all right?
so how are you doing then?
I think it will be truffle
really truffle.
I'm thinking about 300 or so.
now she's separating my order,
I'll put it in.
hand march
supplied
and I won a little award here from the Cocoa show.
it's ours,
very good.
now is to think of strategies that I can
sell fast.
know why the first investment
I did
to validate whether it really works to sell a product
known
and now I've invested more money.
crazy,
what a noise this guy is,
we have to be a little optimistic.
bro,
the car has a bit of a strange noise,
but it's okay.
donut,
I will change a way
and old march,
that's it,
in life everything is 1 question about relationship.
Man,
I'm full of truffle here from the Cocoa Show
and instead of selling on the street,
I go after the places I've been relating to.
Is it on?
I just got here,
the bro already spoke,
he partner,
there is truffle there.
Denis,
mano bought five truffles from Cacau Show
because you already know,
then you're sending me pix there.
now.
and then my cousin is hot.
I invented truffles here at the barbershop
and the bro said that tomorrow it will roll
barbershop anniversary.
said, bro,
comes there old,
why don't you sell some truffles there?
I'm going, I came.
I can get there at Guy's barber shop and
offer my truffles like that,
you know?
ah, I'm selling truffle,
I need to think of some idea and I get
be someone interesting.
I have stock in my hand,
I hope you do.
good,
tô
in this crazy,
there's Rolando 1 sample there,
can prove it.
I will think then.
let's see what I'm going to get ready tomorrow.